CURRICULUM VITAE

Chintan N. Gajjar

Email ID: chintan.gajjar1@gmail.com

Mobile No.: 9712131390

CAREER OBJECTIVE

• My objective is only to Work Hard in the Industry and always to learn something new according to changes in Technology.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION

Examina- tion	Discipline/ Specializa- tion	School/college	Board/ University	Year of Passing	%
B.E	IT Engineer- ing	L.J.I.E.T	GTU	2012	7.26 – (CPI)
HSC	Science + Maths Stream	Swaminarayana- Vidyalaya, Ahmedabad	G.H.S.E.B	2008	72%
SSC	S.S.C	Swaminarayana Vidyalaya, Ahmedabad	G.S.E.B	2006	86.43%
MBA	MBA - IT	Sikkim Manipal University	SMUDE	2016	C

VALUE PROFILE

- An enthusiastic IT professional with 9 years of experience, huge knowledge and expertise
 in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, Woocommerce, API, CSS, SQL, MySQL, HTML5, PHP, CSS3, Magento, Bootstrap, Responsive Web Design, Website Speed Optimisation, Website security, AMP, as well as strong skills and ability in writing clean and efficient code, with excellent troubleshooting and bug resolution abilities.
- Excellent communicator with a patient manner and a high level of professionalism.
- Leadership skill, Value team player, ability to work under pressure and balance multitask assignments.
- Good team member, especially when tough and high-stress goals have to be achieved.

EXPERIENCE

- I have a total of 9 years of experience.
- I have 3 years of experience in Technorigins Web solution Company at CG ROAD, Ahmedabad as **Senior WordPress Developer** from 1 Aug 2013 to 30 July 2016
- 10 months experience in Global Techno Partners Company at Satelite, Ahmedabad as Senior
 WordPress Developer from 1 Sep 2016 to 30 April 2017
- 4-year experience in SmartFish Designs Company at Satelite, Ahmedabad as Team Leader
 & Senior WordPress Developer. from 26 July 2017 to 31 Dec 2021
- Currently Working Remotely in Teacher Tools Private Limited company located in Bangalore

CO-CURRICULAR AND EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Got 2nd prize in the singing competition in Lumina 2012.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Languages : WordPress, PHP, Magento, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Bootstrap, SQL,

Responsive Web Design,

Operating Systems : Mac os x / Ubantu / Windows 10 /

HOBBIES

- Singing
- Playing piano
- Reading books, Travelling

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

- English, Gujarati, Hindi

WORK OVERVIEW

There are many websites on which I have worked on all levels, including designing + responsive and + Coding. So this is a plus point for me to have knowledge in designing also with setting animation layout.

I have mostly worked in WordPress Framework & tried to use different layout combinations with animation effects for the best output.

I have worked on the Magento website too for customization work and have good knowledge to handle the backend system of Magento.

PORTFOLIO:

Please check the below Websites on which I worked earlier. All websites are live. If you have any questions, I can explain any website to you.

http://sikandarfoods.com/

https://isconbalajifoods.com/

http://goldstarpower.com/

https://www.thetiehub.com/

http://www.abilityonwheels.org/

https://www.mukhidairy.com/

https://generiqpharma.com/

http://asiancolourco.com/

http://ektafoods.com/

https://www.mgi-vision.com/

http://ichorexports.com/

https://muskclinic.com/

https://www.alltech-group.com/

http://newpearlceramics.com/

https://www.usbchemicals.com/

And many more.....

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address : A-3, Purna Purushottam So. Part-1, Arjun Ashram Road,

Ranip, Ahmedabad – 382480.

D.O.B : 31-10-1990

Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Indian

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned information.

Place-Ahmedabad

(Chintan Gajjar) 9712131390